hi everyone uh this is guys lapuz your
financial solutions consultants
discuss
set for health so i
product me
insurance so let's proceed on my screen
to begin with our discussion okay
as you could see
and the age for this sample is 49
then the insurance or protection is 1.5
million so of course
[Music]
so yeah yeah
the protection is 1.5 million pesos then
let's go on the next page
discuss nothing new features and
benefits now set for help right
features and benefits now except for
have major critical illness
protection okay the benefit or advantage
ponito i can claim 100
of these i'm assured
protection which is 1.5 million then
three times
he is
so that's 1.5 million then three times
push
so for example
[Music]
let's say cancer
then on the second year
major critical illness then on the third
year
so that's three times fujian majaka
received 900 percent a claim regarding a
critical illness or major critical
illness so 1.5 times three that's
4.5 million
if
[Music]
second now featuring a waiver of premium
so the advantage and benefits non-waiver
opinion if not diagnosed possibly a
major critical illness
[Music]
okay so first year
for example you and your annual is 155
700 pesos and on the second year i'm
gonna then
so yeah
for ten years and then on the fourth
year
on
critical illness
major critical illness
so of course
don't feature in a waiver of premium
summa will wave napoleon fourth year
yeah
download
now remaining payments yeah okay for the
succeeding years
insurance protection
right
now on the next feature in the mind i
marondin among
uh benefit for the minor critical
illness so
known i see i know
minor
the 20 percent of that that's 300 000
pesos so you put you
uh
benefit for the
bus
critical illness
so
basically my minor means
a major critical illness right
then
on the next feature no man of course the
protection or the death benefit if
something happens to victorian if
nawalana pushes a picture
then mario receives
1.5 million
proposal
or quotation
right
then the last one okay
one point five million numericity
beneficiary or normal ones yeah okay
so the last one
i healthy benefit or healthy life
benefit
illness
or any major critical illness or minor
critical illness
healthy 75 years old
on that at the end of that
[Music]
so 155
700 times 10 years that's 1.5
million pressures so ibab
so my babalito
or any
uh purposes or any financial purposes
yeah on that year okay so i guess that's
it that's the set for half
for questions and clarifications message
me
and yeah
have a blessed day everyone
see you on my next videos second part
alright have a blessed day